First, unzip the downloaded zip file and open the .blend file
You will see rigs and models like this one
The collections in the left outline contain the models rig control
The collections in the left outliner contain the models rig control
The collections inthe left outliner contain the models rig control
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode Endo
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode F
Finpers Grasp To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
of.oo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode d
of.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode od
Eesnap Child of.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode d
tosnap child of.e To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
of.oo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
of.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Now you can adjust the pose Lo ofo Recete
Aot Now you can adjust the pose of. e HonModi
Aot Now you can adjust the pose N of. k
Now you can adjust the pose of. tionMoc
Now you can adjust the pose ta
Now you can adjust the pose of.o >
Now you can adjust the pose of.o > Ed Pos
Now you can adjust the pose N Of. e > onMor S
Now you can adjust the pose
Now you can adjust the pose Teo nd
Now you can adjust the pose of.oo AlPose tonMode
Now you can adjust the pose of.oo AlPos
Now you can adjust the pose a of.oo eetAlPose
Now you can adjust the pose of.o Re e tionMoc
Nowyou can adjustthepose
Now you can adjust the pose
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the@owr blenderaddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the@ownloadeefilein rblenderaaddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip includedin thedownloadeg'fileint Urbleneraddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip includedin the@ownloadeefilein Urbleneeraddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloaeeerfilei rblenderaaddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloaaerfilein rblen@erzaddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip includedin the downloaeeerfilein rblen@erzaddor
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloaderfilein rblen@erzaddor Start
Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in thedownloaderfilein rblen@erzaddor Sa
ofe Don't forget to install the rig tools zip included in the@downloadeerfilein rhlonderaaddor
o e of eAlPose PotathooMode
o of eAlPose PotathooMode
e of Resete >
工